[
    {
        "question": "Everglades National Park is located in which US state?",
        "answer": "Florida"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Mexican border city is located south of San Diego?",
        "answer": "Tijuana"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which four US states share a border with Mexico?",
        "answer": "Arizona, California, New Mexico and Texas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the second largest US state in surface area?",
        "answer": "Texas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is located between California and Utah?",
        "answer": "Nevada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which national capital does the Vltava River flow through?",
        "answer": "Prague"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest navigable body of water in the world?",
        "answer": "Lake Titicaca"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which island country`s national language is Malagasy?",
        "answer": "Madagascar"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nation does the island of Okinawa belong to?",
        "answer": "Japan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the most-visited attraction in the UK in 2017?",
        "answer": "British Museum"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city has the biggest helicopter fleet in the world?",
        "answer": "Sao Paulo"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a `foss` in Iceland?",
        "answer": "A waterfall"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which U.S. state did the world`s largest recorded snowflake fall?",
        "answer": "Montana"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. state has the longest width east to west?",
        "answer": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state is Crater Lake found?",
        "answer": "Oregon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Trinidad and Tobago are a part of which continent?",
        "answer": "North America"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chablis comes from which French wine region? ",
        "answer": "Burgundy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Bermuda?",
        "answer": "Hamilton"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hamilton is the capital of which British Overseas Territory?",
        "answer": "Bermuda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state is the Hoover Dam located in?",
        "answer": "It lies on the border between Arizona and Nevada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Cyprus?",
        "answer": "Nicosia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Hawaiian dish resembles a bowl of deconstructed sushi?",
        "answer": "Poke -- Poke (POH-kay) can be traced to the Polynesians, who preserved raw fish with salt. The original dish contained mainly reef fish, candlenut, and seaweed."
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country was the largest known T-Rex skeleton found?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the nickname of the oft photographed, colorful row of houses in Cobh, Ireland?",
        "answer": "Deck of Cards -- Cobh is famous for its quaint, brightly painted houses, but none are as famous as the ones lining a hilly street close to the coast."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city is the capital of Australia?",
        "answer": "Canberra"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where in the United States is coffee grown?",
        "answer": "Hawaii and California"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a better known name for the Hellenic Republic?",
        "answer": "Greece"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country contains Lake Assal, the lowest point on mainland Africa?",
        "answer": "Djibouti"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the Seven Wonders of the World was situated approximately 50 miles south of modern Baghdad?",
        "answer": "The Hanging Gardens of Babylon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color is the cross on the Swedish flag?",
        "answer": "Yellow"
    },
    {
        "question": "What bird is New Zealand`s national symbol?",
        "answer": "The Kiwi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which South American country shares its name with a nut?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many U.S. states are there?",
        "answer": "Fifty"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most popular spirit produced in Jamaica?",
        "answer": "Rum"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country invented the popular dessert known as banoffee pie?",
        "answer": "England -- Featuring a buttery biscuit base topped with gooey bananas, toffee, and whipped cream, it was created by Ian Dowding."
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city can you find the Helix Bridge?",
        "answer": "Singapore -- Located in Singapore`s Marina Bay, the Helix Bridge was modeled after the helical shape of a DNA strand."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the former name of Istanbul?",
        "answer": "Constantinople"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Pennsylvania Station?",
        "answer": "New York City"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest of the islands off the southern coast of Cape Cod?",
        "answer": "Martha`s Vineyard"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Blyde River Canyon, one of the largest canyons on Earth?",
        "answer": "South Africa -- At more than 16 miles long and 2,624 feet (26 km) deep, it is one of South Africa`s most spectacular natural wonders."
    },
    {
        "question": "What South American country is a former Dutch colony?",
        "answer": "Suriname"
    },
    {
        "question": "How are U-shaped valleys formed?",
        "answer": "Ice"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most earthquake-prone state?",
        "answer": "Alaska"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is serviced by O`Hare International Airport?",
        "answer": "Chicago"
    },
    {
        "question": "What island in California was once called Pelican Island?",
        "answer": "Alcatraz Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city was originally called Terminus in 1837?",
        "answer": "Atlanta"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is serviced by Dulles International Airport?",
        "answer": "Washington D.C."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the third largest US state in surface area?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is known as the `Hoosier State`?",
        "answer": "Indiana"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state has the longest land border with Canada?",
        "answer": "Alaska"
    }
]